[rock guitar riff playing]
‎奶酪节
Cheese festival.
‎（威斯康辛密尔沃基最新动态）
‎又一个奶酪节
Another cheese festival.
‎等等
Hold up.
‎密尔沃基有场仓库锐舞派对
There's a warehouse rave in Milwaukee.
‎我要去 我想去个用不着忍耐的地方
I need this. I want to go somewhere
where I don't have to hold back.
‎-你一直在忍耐吗？
‎-你根本想不到
You've been holding back?
‎-你一直在忍耐吗？
‎-你根本想不到
You have no idea.
‎我是不知道
I don't know.
‎上次我去锐舞排队时
‎我足足两天两夜没睡
Last time I went to a rave,
I stayed up for two days.
‎事实证明 如果一颗薄荷糖
‎要价40块 那就不是普通的薄荷糖
Turns out, if a mint is 40 bucks,
it's not a mint.
‎好故事 但我还是想去
Great story.
I still want to go.
‎你们知道我想要什么吗？
You know what I want?
‎别说是杰伊
Don't say Jay.
‎杰伊
Jay.
[Ozzie groans]
‎他没吻我的那天晚上 真是太火辣了
It was so hot when he didn't kiss me
on the car the other night.
‎那是什么意思？我们会怎么样？
What does it mean? Where is it going?
‎我要不要把腿后面的汗毛刮了？
Should I start shaving
the back of my legs?
‎莉亚 把你所有的个人价值
‎都交付在一名男性手中
Leia, placing all of your value
in the hands of a man
‎那就全都白白浪费了
is just giving it away,
‎这就是生活在
‎压迫性父权社会中的恶果
and the result of living
in an oppressive patriarchal society.
‎她读了《暴女宣言》之后
‎就开始喋喋不休讲个不停
She read the "Riot Grrrl Manifesto"
and won't shut up about it.
‎我想成为女权主义者
I want to be a feminist.
‎在大学里
In college.
‎但是 现在 我真的想要个男朋友
But right now,
I really, really, really want a boyfriend.
‎你没吻她？
You didn't kiss her?
‎来自点域镇凯尔索家的杰伊凯尔索？
Jay Kelso, of the Point Place Kelsos?
‎整个镇上最淫荡的家庭？
The horniest family in town?
‎我不知道我是怎么了
I don't know what came over me.
‎我是说 我脑海里总有个声音
‎在说：“捏爆她的奶子 老兄”
I mean, there's one voice in my head
saying, "Honk her boob, bro."
‎这声音一直在我耳边 所以这很正常
But he's always there, so that's normal.
‎奇怪的是 那天有另一个
‎十分甜美的声音跟我说：“不 哥们
The weird part was there was
this other sweet voice saying, "No, bro."
‎打动她的芳心”
"Honk her heart."
‎嘿 等等 你知道
‎这意味着什么吧？你喜欢她
Hey, wait.
You know what this means, right?
‎嘿 等等 你知道
‎这意味着什么吧？你喜欢她
You like her.
‎不会吧…是吗？
No… Right?
‎不会吧
No.
‎没错 那个甜美的声音就是这个意思
‎你终于把她当作平等的人来看待了
Yes, that's what that sweet voice means.
You're seeing her as a person.
‎太诡异了
Weird.
‎莉亚 我不确定
‎你是不是已经准备好接受杰伊了
Leia, I'm not sure
if you're ready for Jay.
‎他是个花花公子
He's a player.
‎你才刚刚献出你的初吻
‎杰伊却已经在湖里跟人打炮了
You just had your first kiss.
‎你才刚刚献出你的初吻
‎杰伊却已经在湖里跟人打炮了
Jay's had sex in a lake.
‎我甚至不愿意在湖里洗脸
I don't even like
to put my face in a lake.
‎我们可不希望你最终
We don't want you to end up being
‎只是他的暑期炮友
‎在开学前就被他甩了
some summer hookup
he dumps before school starts.
‎上个劳动节可真是惨烈啊
Last Labor Day was a massacre.
‎我从没见过那么多詹妮弗
‎在同一条车道上痛哭流涕
I've never seen so many Jennifers
crying in the same driveway.
‎你得赶紧把这事情了结了
You need to close the deal ASAP.
‎告诉莉亚你喜欢她就好 我们走吧
Just tell Leia you like her. Let's go.
‎我办不到
I can't.
‎我爸总跟我说
‎千万不要先跟女孩子说你喜欢她
My dad always told me
to never tell a girl you like her first.
‎这样她们就全权掌控了这段感情关系
It gives them all the control
in the relationship.
‎才不是这样的
[scoffs] That's not true.
‎是我先对妮基下手的
‎而现在完全由我说了算
I made the first move with Nikki,
and I am totally in the driver's seat.
‎没错 宝贝
That's right, babe.
‎老兄 她让你戴着她爸以前的
‎医用传呼机 以防她有什么需要
Dude, she makes you wear her dad's old
doctor pager in case she needs something.
‎嘿 我只会在紧急情况下使用
Hey, I only use it for emergencies.
‎-没错 就像昨晚
‎-昨晚你需要什么来着？
-Yeah, like last night.
-And what did you need last night?
‎口香糖
Gum.
‎紧急口香糖
Emergency gum.
‎你们真的了解杰伊吗？
Are you guys sure about Jay?
‎男人才不会
‎假装这么贴心呢 这有什么意义？
A guy's not just gonna
pretend to be sweet.
‎男人才不会
‎假装这么贴心呢 这有什么意义？
What would be the point of that?
‎教她可真费劲
We don't get paid enough.
‎好吧 听着 如果你铁了心
‎要跟那个湖中猛男约会
Okay, look. If you're dead set
on dating that lake humper,
‎至少得机灵点
at least be smart about it.
‎别就这么对他投怀送抱
Don't throw yourself at him.
‎你是女神 掌控自己的权力
You are a goddess. Own your power.
‎你说得对
You're right.
‎-我要确保她先来找我表白
‎-我要确保他先来找我表白
[both] I'm going to make sure…
‎-我要确保她先来找我表白
‎-我要确保他先来找我表白
-…he comes to me first.
-…she comes to me first.
‎一 二 三 四
-[rock music plays]
-One, two, three, four!
‎在街上闲逛
♪ Hangin' out down the street ♪
‎和上周没什么两样
♪ The same old thing we did last week ♪
‎没什么事好做 就跟你唠唠嗑
♪ Not a thing to do ♪
♪ But talk to you ♪
‎这样挺好 这样挺好
♪ We're all all right! ♪
♪ We're all all right! ♪
‎你好 威斯康辛！
‎（90年代秀）
[young woman] Hello, Wisconsin!
‎我喜欢《法律与秩序》
Now, I love Law & Order.
‎第一部分是关于法律的
‎第二部分是关于秩序的
The first part is about law,
and the second part is about order.
‎非常令人满足
It's very satisfying.
‎没错 标题差不多就是这么说的
Yep, the title pretty much explains it.
‎还有《亲爱的 我把孩子缩小了》
Like Honey, I Shrunk the Kids.
‎他把孩子缩小了
‎现在他不得不告诉他老婆
He shrunk his kids,
and now he has to tell his wife.
‎我被剧透了个遍
I'm all caught up.
‎凯蒂 看电视的意义就在于
Kitty, the whole point of watching TV
‎我们不必彼此交流
is so we don't have to talk to each other.
‎好吧 那我闭嘴
All right, I'll hush up.
[exhales sharply]
‎我有没有告诉你
‎那天莉亚有多可爱吗？
Did I tell you how adorable
Leia was the other day?
‎我们在用明星的名字给意大利面起名
We were coming up with
celebrity pasta names.
‎我想出了“斜管面与泰勒”
I said Penne and Teller.
[chuckles]
‎她想出了“马基马克通心粉”
She said Marky Markaroni.
‎你瞧 对她来说
‎我不只是她的奶奶 我是…
You know, I… I'm more than
just a grandma to her. I'm…
‎我们是可以一块出去浪的朋友
We are friends and hang out.
‎出去浪？
Hang out?
‎你知道谁会
‎跟他们的父母一块出去浪吗？
You know who hung out with their parents?
‎梅内德斯兄弟
The Menendez brothers.
‎好吧
Well.
‎我不喜欢谋杀
I'm not a fan of the murders.
‎但我挺喜欢他们的毛衣
But a big fan of the sweaters.
‎听着…
Look… [coughs]
‎我们不该和小毛孩做朋友
We are not meant to be friends with kids.
‎他们总是在…吃拿卡要
They're always eating, taking…
clogging things.
‎你刚转过身去一秒钟
You turn your back for one second,
‎不知哪个蠢货
‎就在你的马桶里塞了一整条面包
and some dumbass has put
a loaf of bread in your toilet.
Oh!
‎粗纹管面托尼丹扎
Rigatony Danza!
‎粗纹管面托尼丹扎 莉亚
Rigatony Danza! Leia! Leia!
[funky rock music playing]
‎所以你的计划就是
‎给自己浑身上下都抹上油
So your plan is to just oil yourself up
‎然后蹲在外面
‎等着莉亚给你抛媚眼吗？
and wait out here
for Leia to catch a hot glimpse?
‎你忘了 我还带着吉他
You forgot. I also brought my guitar.
‎好吧 抹太多油了
Okay, too much oil.
‎你真做作
Ugh! You're so cheesy.
‎她一定喜欢得不得了
She's gonna love it.
‎嗨 妮可
[panting] Hey, Nik. I got your page.
‎我收到你的传呼
‎给你家打了电话 你妈说你在这儿
I called your house,
but your mom said you were here.
‎我需要来个肩颈按摩
I need some of this on my shoulders.
‎没问题 宝贝
Oh. 'Course, babe.
‎确实完全由你说了算
-Yeah, you're in the driver's seat.
-[chuckles]
‎你认真的吗？
[Gwen] Seriously?
‎你看起来像根淋湿的热狗
You look like a wet hot dog.
‎谢了 格温
Thanks, Gwen.
‎嗨 美女
Hey, girl.
‎杰伊 嗨
Jay, hi.
‎我是说 嗨 贾伊 杰伊 贾伊
I mean, hi, Jai. Jay. Jai.
‎贾伊
Jai. [chuckles]
Jai.
‎我喜欢这名字
I like that.
‎这可以作为你对我的可爱昵称
That can be your cute nickname for me.
[chuckles]
‎好的
Okay. [giggles]
‎不好 我们走吧
Not okay. Let's go.
‎或者你可以留在这儿
Or you can stay here.
‎比如 跟贾伊…一块聊聊
You know, hang with… Jai.
‎-我可以跟你谈谈吗？
‎-当然可以
-Could I talk to you for a second?
-Sure.
‎好
Okay.
‎你为啥活像杰伊的皮条客似的？
Why are you acting like Jay's pimp?
‎我想让他勾搭上莉亚
‎这样他就不会来烦我和内特了
I'm trying to get him coupled up with Leia
so he'll leave me and Nate alone.
‎他们会共享甜筒
‎杰伊得了接吻病 结果我也得了
They share ice cream cones.
When Jay had mono, I got it.
‎我不想让她成为
‎杰伊的另一个暑期炮友
I don't want her to be
another one of Jay's summer lays.
‎不会的 他是真的喜欢她
It's not like that. He actually likes her.
‎那他可以像个绅士一样约她出去
Then he can ask her out like a gentleman.
‎他不会这么做的
He won't do that.
‎他的家规之类的不允许他这么做
It's not allowed in his family
or something.
‎好吧 嗯 她也不会
‎看来我们没什么好说的了
Okay, well, she's not going to either,
so I guess we're done.
‎明白了吧 关键在于动动手指
See, it's all about moving the fingers.
[Leia giggles]
‎我能感觉到你在我耳边说话
I can feel you talking in my ear.
‎莉亚
Leia!
‎抱歉 我得走了
[scoffs] Sorry, I have to go.
‎这怎么会没用呢？
How did that not work?
‎我的意思是 我甚至问我爸
‎借来他的CK一号到处都喷
I mean, I even borrowed my dad's CK One
and put it everywhere.
‎你闻上去真香
You smell great!
‎能给我匀一点吗 老兄？
Can I get a little of that, bro?
‎来吧
Get in here!
[beeping]
‎谁在呼我？
Who's paging me?
[loud dialing]
‎哪位
Hello.
‎嗨 克莱恩医生
[in deep voice] Oh. Hi, Dr. Klein.
‎是个医生 他以为我是妮基的爸爸
[whispers] It's some doctor.
He thinks I'm Nikki's dad.
‎快挂了
Hang up.
‎或者…
Or…
‎嗯哼
[in deep voice] Uh-huh.
‎没错 我同意这应该被切除
Yes, I agree, that should be removed.
‎好的 很棒
Okay, sweet. [chuckles]
‎再见
Bye. [giggles]
‎老兄
Bro.
‎我刚刚成了名医生
I just doctored!
‎肃然起敬 老兄
Mad respect, bro.
‎老兄医生
Doctor Bro.
[funky rock music playing]
‎-嗨
‎-早上好
-Hi.
-Good morning.
‎你怎么进我房间的？
How did you get in my room?
‎我从窗户爬进来的
I climbed through the window.
‎那我们该聊些什么？
‎杰伊？好的 没问题
So what should we talk about?
Jay? Okay, sure.
‎我觉得你该去追他
I think you should go for it.
‎-不行
‎-为什么不行？
-I can't.
-Why not?
‎这是怎么回事？
What the hell is this?
‎你不是应该
‎用你的肉体控制我哥哥的人生吗？
Shouldn't you be controlling
my brother's life with your body?
‎他就像一头性奋的僵尸
He's like a zombie with a boner.
‎嗯 莉亚 内特和我有两张
‎今晚的《永远的蝙蝠侠》电影票
So, Leia, Nate and I have
Batman Forever tickets tonight.
‎但我在想 你和杰伊没准用得上
But I was thinking,
you and Jay could use them
‎在黑暗中…勾勾搭搭…
‎周围也没有烦人的家伙
and hang out… in the dark…
with no annoying people around.
‎我很乐意…婉拒了哈
‎因为我今晚有安排了
I would love to
‎我很乐意…婉拒了哈
‎因为我今晚有安排了
pass on that because I have plans tonight.
‎真的吗？
Oh, really?
‎跟我说说你有什么“安排”
Tell me more about these "plans."
‎我们要去…
Um… we're going to, um…
‎密尔沃基的锐舞派对
A rave in Milwaukee!
‎对
Uh, yeah.
‎没错 锐舞派对
Totally. A rave.
‎我以为在你被邻居家的狗门
I thought you were
taking a break from raves
‎卡住之后 就准备暂别锐舞派对了
after you got stuck
in your neighbor's doggy door.
‎我以为那是纳尼亚的入口
I thought it was Narnia.
‎那不是
It wasn't.
‎如果你们全都要去这个
‎货真价实的锐舞派对 那我们也要去
Okay, well, if you're all going
to this totally real rave, then so are we.
‎酷 到时候见
Cool. See you there.
‎锐舞派对？你为什么要这么说？
A rave?! Why did you say that?
‎纯粹出于一己之私
For purely selfish reasons.
‎我不行
I can't.
‎锐舞派对既危险又违法
‎而且那里的卫生间到底什么状况？
Raves are dangerous and illegal.
And what even is the bathroom situation?
‎我有公厕恐惧症
‎我在图书馆里几乎都尿不出来
I'm a shy pee-er.
I can barely pee at the library.
‎放松 那里会有很多卫生间的
Relax. There'll be plenty of bathrooms.
‎每个人都要去那里打炮和嗑药
That's where everyone goes
to have sex and do drugs.
‎什么？算了
What?! Forget it.
‎我…这已经远超出了我的舒适区
I… This is way out of my comfort zone.
‎再说了 我爷爷奶奶是不会让我去的
Besides, my grandparents
would never let me go.
‎那就撒谎吧
Then lie.
‎对着他们可爱的小脸蛋？
To their sweet little faces?
‎我这辈子都做不到
I could never do that.
‎电影？听起来很有趣
A movie? That sounds fun.
‎对 《永远的蝙蝠侠》
Yep. [chuckles] Batman Forever.
‎-得到了相当锐意的热评
‎-伙计
-It's getting rave reviews.
-Dude.
‎不是锐意的热评 而是好坏参半
Um, I mean, not rave reviews.
Mixed reviews.
‎你发现了！我撒谎了
You caught me! I lied!
‎我是说 去看电影的事我没撒谎
I mean, I didn't lie
about going to the movies.
‎但那些锐…热评 我撒了谎
I lied about the rave…
reviews!
‎我们该走了
We should get going.
‎再见 奶奶 再见 爷爷
‎今晚锐得愉快
Bye, Grandma. Bye, Grandpa.
Rave a good night!
‎好好看电影
Enjoy the movie!
‎他们在撒谎
They're lying.
‎莉亚是不会这么对我的
‎她是我的意面搭档
Oh, Leia wouldn't do that to me.
‎莉亚是不会这么对我的
‎她是我的意面搭档
She's my pasta pal.
‎该死 我忘了告诉她“直面墨菲”了
Oh, darn it. I forgot to tell her
about Spaghetti Murphy.
[rock music playing]
‎哇
Wow.
‎那些女孩都是半裸着的
Those girls are half naked.
[dance music playing faintly]
‎真是太可怕了
And it's terrible.
‎-为什么你闻起来活像猫尿？
‎-为了和莉亚水到渠成
Why do you smell like cat pee?
‎-为什么你闻起来活像猫尿？
‎-为了和莉亚水到渠成
To close the deal with Leia,
‎我在身上喷了很多这种信息素香水
I put on a bunch of these pheromones
‎是我通过健美杂志后面的广告买来的
I bought from the back
of my bodybuilding magazine.
‎老虎汗水
Tiger Sweat. [chuckles]
‎太牛逼了
That's badass.
‎这种气味会让女士们无法抗拒
Ladies find the scent irresistible.
‎这辆小货车闻起来好像厕所
Ugh! The van smells like ass.
‎我有种不祥的预感
‎我们好像忘了什么事情
I got a terrible feeling
we didn't do something.
‎-我有带荧光棒吗？
‎-带了
-Did I bring the glow sticks?
-Yeah.
‎奶嘴我也都带了吗？
Did I bring all the pacifiers?
‎没有 但我带了
No, I did.
‎我们还能忘带什么呢？
What else could we be forgetting?
‎奥兹！
Ozzie!
[screaming]
‎我在车道上发现了这玩意儿
I found this in the driveway.
‎你还认为他们在看电影吗？
Still think they're at the movies?
‎哦 我们先…
Well, let's…
‎我们先别急着下结论
Let's not jump to conclusions.
‎奥兹 亲爱的
Ozzie, sweetie,
‎为什么你看起来像是
‎我嗑了安眠药之后梦见的东西？
why do you look like something
from one of my sleeping pill dreams?
‎他暂且
He's not talking.
‎不肯说
Yet.
‎说吧…我的孙女在哪里？
Now… where's my granddaughter?
‎在和我妈谈过之前
‎我是什么都不会说的
I'm not saying jack squat
until I talk to my mother.
‎除非你开口说话
‎否则你再也见不到你妈了
You'll never see your mother again
until you start talking.
[sighs]
‎行 好吧
Okay, fine.
‎她去了“关你”
She went to nunya.
‎总算现在有点进展了
Now we're getting somewhere.
‎“关你”在哪里？
Where's nunya?
‎关你屁事
Nunya business.
‎哦 雷德
‎你简直…你简直就是自投罗网啊
Well, Red, you kinda…
You just kinda walked into that.
[rock music playing]
‎-你怎么能不等奥兹就直接开走了？
‎-什么？可别怪我
-How could you drive off without Ozzie?
-What? Don't blame me.
‎我在给人安排输血 所以有点分心了
I was a little distracted
ordering a blood transfusion.
‎-什么？
‎-别担心
-What?
-Don't worry about it.
‎卫生间的事情你说对了 太疯狂了
You were right about the bathroom.
It was crazy.
‎有个女孩还坐在马桶上就想过来抱我
Some girl tried to hug me on the toilet.
[Leia sighs]
‎我受够了
‎我要表现得成熟点 好好跟杰伊谈谈
I've had enough.
‎我受够了
‎我要表现得成熟点 好好跟杰伊谈谈
I'm gonna do the mature thing
and talk to Jay.
‎拿着我的奶嘴
Hold my binky.
‎嘿 杰伊
Hey, Jay.
‎我们能不能就这么好好聊聊
‎而不是像现在这样不知道在做啥？
Um, can we just talk to each other
instead of whatever it is we're doing?
‎很高兴你这么说了
Oh, I'm so glad you said that.
‎我们本来挺好的
‎结果现在大家都掺和进来了
We had a nice thing going,
and now everyone got involved.
‎-然后就变得诡异起来了
‎-没错
-It just got weird.
-Exactly.
‎不如 我们数到三
‎然后一块说出各自的感受
How about, on the count of three,
we both just say how we feel?
‎好啊
Great.
‎一、二、三
[both] One, two, three.
‎-我喜欢你
‎-我就知道
-I like you.
-I knew it!
‎什么？不 你耍了我
‎没关系 你已经说出来了
-What? No, you tricked me.
-Well, it doesn't matter. You said it.
[scoffs]
‎我的天啊 大家都是对的
‎你…你是个花花公子
Oh my God. Everyone's right.
You… You're a player.
‎嘿 对于像我这样跟许多漂亮妞
Hey. That's an ugly stereotype
‎约会过的帅哥来说
‎这是个丑恶的刻板印象
for hot guys like me
who date lots of chicks.
‎你知道吗？我确实喜欢你
[scoffs] You know what? I did like you.
‎但我喜欢的是那个
‎在车上既贴心又真诚的家伙
I liked that guy on the car
who was sweet and sincere.
‎而不是这家伙 这家伙烂透了
But not this guy. This guy sucks.
‎行 没关系 不管你喜不喜欢我
Well, fine. It doesn't matter
if you're into me or not.
‎这个仓库里到处都是辣妹
‎而我闻起来像只老虎
There's a warehouse
full of hot girls in there,
‎这个仓库里到处都是辣妹
‎而我闻起来像只老虎
and I smell like a tiger.
‎像…老虎的屁眼
A tiger's butthole!
‎这里也有不少男生
‎今晚谁玩得更开心 我们等着瞧
And there are guys in there too.
We'll see who has a better night.
‎你还没见过我的舞步呢
And you haven't seen my moves.
‎我的胳膊怎么了？
‎它感受到了音乐 这就是原因
What happened to my arm?
‎我的胳膊怎么了？
‎它感受到了音乐 这就是原因
It's feeling the music! That's what!
‎那就祝你好运啦
Okay. Good luck in there.
[scoffs]
[loud, pulsing dance music playing]
‎杰伊瞧见我有多开心了吗？
[talking over music]
Is Jay seeing how much fun I'm having?
‎很难说 有那么多女孩围着他
It's hard to tell.
He's surrounded by so many girls.
‎砰！
Pow.
‎嗨呀！
Hi-yah!
‎空手道！
Karate!
‎我得加把劲了
[Leia] I need to step it up.
‎你没事吧？
Are you okay?
‎你需要医疗救助吗？
Do you need medical help?
‎那家伙是个医生
That guy's a doctor.
‎照X光！
X-ray!
‎哪个？
Which one?
‎全都要！
All of them.
‎奥兹…
Ozzie…
‎亲爱的…
Honey…
‎显然 你在这套装束上费了很大功夫
Obviously, you put a ton of work
into that costume.
[gasps] Thank you for noticing.
‎-感谢你注意到了
‎-这个波浪花边的针脚 哇哦！
I mean, the stitching on the rickrack.
‎-感谢你注意到了
‎-这个波浪花边的针脚 哇哦！
Wow!
‎我想让你知道 我认识到了你的价值
I want you to know that I see you.
‎我为你感到骄傲
And I'm proud of you.
‎你的小蛋蛋真是让我为之倾倒
And I am dazzled
by your little balls.
‎好吧 福尔曼太太
‎我会告诉你莉亚在哪里
Okay, Mrs. Forman.
I'll tell you where Leia is.
‎看到了吗 雷德？
See, Red?
‎如果你信任他们 尊重他们
If you trust them,
and you… you treat them with respect,
‎他们就会对你坦诚相待
they will be honest with you.
‎莉亚在密尔沃基的锐舞派对上
Leia's at a rave in Milwaukee.
‎那个撒谎的小贱人
That lying little bitch.
[rock music playing]
[loud dance music resumes]
‎你一直在回复我爸的医用传呼吗？
You've been answering
my dad's doctor pages?
‎我做得可棒了 妮可
I did pretty well, Nik.
‎我被邀请去参加丹佛的一个会议
I got invited to a conference in Denver.
‎他跟人勾搭上了
He's coupled off.
‎我该怎么办？
What should I do?
‎也许不要只跟我一块跳舞了
Maybe stop dancing with just me.
‎我在考虑
On it.
‎该死 我特喵的完蛋了
Oh f**k. I'm f**king f**ked.
‎没错
Yep.
‎所以 目前为止
‎我和男人最深入的交流
So, to date,
the furthest I've gotten with a guy
‎就是跟我爷爷在锐舞派对上拉拉扯扯
was grinding on my grandpa at a rave.
‎没事 这也不算毫无进展了
‎至少他带你回家了
Well, it's not nothing.
He took you home with him.
‎这不好笑 格温 他会杀了我的
This isn't funny, Gwen.
He's gonna kill me.
‎对不起 感觉这似乎是我的错
I'm sorry. This kinda feels like my fault.
‎因为这确实都是你的错
That's because it's all your fault.
‎我本想让你振作起来 但说实话
I was trying to empower you,
but, to be honest,
‎那个暴女文化
‎之类的东西 我只是略知皮毛
I only skimmed
that whole riot grrrl thing.
‎但是 真要我说的话 最重要的是
But, if I had to guess
what it's all about,
‎你该做任何你想做的事情
‎不该有任何人来阻拦你
you should get to do what you want
without anyone holding you back,
‎也包括我
including me.
‎所以 如果你还喜欢杰伊的话
‎那就去找他吧
So, if you still want Jay,
then go get him.
‎今晚过后
‎我已经不知道自己想要什么了
After tonight, I don't know what I want.
‎不管怎样 我可能先该跟我爷爷分手
Either way, I should probably
break up with my grandpa first.
[both chuckle]
‎格温 出去
Gwen.
Get out.
‎这是“关你”
This is nunya.
‎关你屁事
Nunya business.
‎我真的很抱歉 各位
I'm so sorry, you guys.
‎但是 奶奶 你该知道
‎我心中只有奶油白酱后悔宽面
But, Grandma, you should know,
I feel nothing but regrettuccine Alfredo.
‎行 那就好
Okay, that was good.
‎但奶奶很生气
But Grandma's pissed.
‎我对你太失望了
I am so disappointed in you.
‎你利用了我的信任 我的爱
You took advantage of my trust, my love,
‎还拿走了我所有好用的安全别针
and all of my good safety pins.
‎-我确实犯了个错
‎-嗯哼
-I really messed up.
-[Kitty] Uh-huh.
‎好吧 你将禁足一周
Well, you are grounded for a week.
‎不准看电视 不准玩任天堂
‎还有那个你很喜欢的绿草娃娃？
No cable, no Nintendo.
‎不准看电视 不准玩任天堂
‎还有那个你很喜欢的绿草娃娃？
And that Chia Pet you like so much?
‎我要把它放在冰箱里直到它死掉
I'm gonna put it in the freezer
until it dies.
‎雷德 你还有什么要补充的吗？
Red, do you have anything to add?
‎没了
No.
‎只是…我们很高兴你安全到家了 孩子
Just that… we're glad
you're home safe, kiddo.
‎就这？
That's it?
‎嗯 我已经看了不少《法律与秩序》
‎我知道必须得有个人来扮演好警察
Well, I've seen enough Law & Order
to know that there has to be a good cop.
‎那么 我是坏警察咯？
So, I'm the bad cop?
‎我喜欢
Oh, I like this.
‎-这就是你一直以来的感受吗？
‎-哦 当然啦
-Is this how you feel all the time?
-Oh yeah.
‎你真坏
[laughs] You are bad!
[Kitty laughs]
‎-哦 你们呀
‎-没错 不 回你的房间去
-Aw, you guys.
-Yeah, no. Go to your room.
‎-嘿
‎-嘿 我听说你被禁足了
Hey.
‎-嘿
‎-嘿 我听说你被禁足了
Hey. I heard you were grounded.
‎我也被骂了
I got busted too.
‎那个老虎汗水之类的东西
‎在我们的地毯上烧了个洞
That Tiger Sweat stuff
burned a hole in our carpet.
‎现在我妈气死了
Now my mom's pissed.
‎听着…我只是想为事情的进展道歉
Look… I just wanted to apologize
for how things went.
‎没关系
It's okay.
‎我们都有点情绪上头了
We both got kinda caught up in it.
‎听着…我确实是你以为的那种人
[sighs] Look, I really am the guy
you thought I was.
‎好吗？我不想再处处留情了
Okay? I'm done playing games.
‎不如 我们数到三
‎然后一块说出各自的感受？
How about, on the count of three,
we both say how we feel about each other?
‎-这次是真的
‎-好的
-For real this time.
-Okay.
‎一、二、三
[both] One, two, three.
‎-我喜欢你
‎-我觉得我们还是做朋友比较好
-I like you.
-I think we should just be friends.
‎等等 做朋友？
Wait, friends?
‎-对
‎-就像罗斯和瑞秋？
-Yeah.
-Like Ross and Rachel?
‎更像乔伊和钱德勒
More like Joey and Chandler.
‎夏天没那么长 别把事情搞复杂了
Look, the summer's not that long.
Let's not complicate it.
‎那么做朋友？
So, friends?
‎当然 做朋友
Sure. Friends.
‎做朋友？他说完那些话之后？
Friends? After he said all that?
‎我真是搞不懂
I'm so confused.
‎他也是
So is he.
‎现在所有权力都归我了
Now I have all the power.
‎这是个战略举措
It was a move.
‎我玩弄了花花公子
‎我用了凯尔索的招数来对付凯尔索
I played the player. I Kelsoed the Kelso.
‎我…需要你来告诉我
‎我没把这一切都搞砸
I…
‎我…需要你来告诉我
‎我没把这一切都搞砸
need you to tell me
I didn't screw it all up.
‎太有心机 太狡猾了
It's so manipulative and sneaky.
‎我喜欢
I love it.
‎嘿！我还在生气呢
Hey! I'm still mad.
‎少说话 多锐舞
Less talk, more rave.
[electronic dance music playing]
[rock music playing]
‎字幕翻译：Zeo Niu